<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.terminaltabtailor.TerminalTabTailor</id>
  <name>Terminal Tab Tailor</name>
  <vendor email="romain.dalichamp@gmail.com" url="http://romain.dalichamp.fr">Terminal Tab Tailor
  </vendor>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <b>What's New in TerminalTabTailor 1.1.0</b>
    <br/><br/>
    <b>Improvements:</b>
    <ul>
      <li><b>Improved Sorting of Terminal Tabs:</b> Terminal tabs are now automatically sorted whenever settings are updated and the new configuration is applied.</li>
      <li><b>Customizable Sorting Order:</b> Users can now choose between ascending and descending order for sorting by date, with ascending order set as the default.</li>
      <li><b>Enhanced Date Sorting:</b> When sorting by date, tabs are now organized in ascending order for each specific date.</li>
      <li><b>Handling Tabs Without Dates:</b> Tabs lacking a date or with dates that do not match the expected pattern are now moved to the end of the list and sorted in ascending order.</li>
    </ul>
    <br/><br/>
    <b>Refactor:</b>
    <ul>
      <li><b>Optimization for Responsiveness:</b> Implemented read operations for executing slow tasks, enhancing performance and responsiveness by offloading heavy computations from the Event Dispatcher Thread.</li>
      <li><b>Enhanced Tab Management:</b> Tabs are now automatically re-sorted following each rename operation, ensuring consistent order and organization.</li>
    </ul>
  ]]></change-notes>

  <description><![CDATA[
    Terminal Tab Tailor significantly enhances the IntelliJ IDEA workflow by dynamically renaming terminal tabs to reflect the currently selected item in your project tree. This feature greatly aids in organizing your workspace and navigating effortlessly between numerous terminal sessions.
    <br/><br/>
    Simply select a file or folder within your project tree and initiate a terminal session from that context.
    <br/><br/>
    Configurability is at the heart of Terminal Tab Tailor; venture into the settings to tailor its behavior to your needs:
    <ul>
      <li>Prompt the renaming dialogue each time a new terminal tab is opened.</li>
      <li>Maintain tabs in perpetual alphabetical order.</li>
      <li>Maintain tabs sorted by descending date.</li>
      <li>Incorporate the current date into tab names (with a customizable pattern, defaulting to dd-MM-YY).</li>
    </ul>
    <br/><br/>
    Choose from a variety of naming conventions to suit your workflow:<br/>
    <ul>
      <li>Permit the use of file names directly.</li>
      <li>Default to directory names, utilizing the parent directory's name for files.</li>
      <li>Adopt the name of the parent module.</li>
      <li>Use the parent module's directory name for a more structured approach.</li>
      <li>Consistently use the project's name for all terminal tabs.</li>
    </ul>
    <br/><br/>
    <b>Pro-tip</b>: Enhance your efficiency by assigning a shortcut to the "Open In > Terminal" action, streamlining the process of opening terminals in your desired context.
  ]]></description>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  <depends>org.jetbrains.plugins.terminal</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <postStartupActivity implementation="com.terminaltabtailor.activities.StartupActivity"/>
    <projectConfigurable parentId="tools"
      instance="com.terminaltabtailor.settings.TerminalTabTailorConfigurable"
      displayName="Terminal Tab Tailor"/>
    <applicationService
      serviceImplementation="com.terminaltabtailor.settings.TerminalTabTailorSettingsService"/>
  </extensions>

  <application-components>
    <component>
      <implementation-class>com.terminaltabtailor.activities.StartupActivity</implementation-class>
    </component>
  </application-components>
</idea-plugin>